Select a School...

Select a School

Search Our Site  [](javascript:; "Search")

Our Schools

Our Schools

    "

    "* [Choose BCPS](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/26445)

    "* [District Initiatives](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/12478)

    "* [Welcome: Office of Academics](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/12593)
    
    * [Applied Learning (Academic Electives, Specials & Magnet Programs)](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/34542)
    
    "* [Administrative Locations](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/13383)
    * [Regional Superintendents and Assistant Superintendent Offices](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/24869)
    
    * [Regional Superintendent and Assistant Superintendent Offices - Overview](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/76651)
    
    "* [Watch Board Meetings and Workshops](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/35670)
    
    * [Meeting Minutes and Recaps / Workshop Summaries / Past Amendments / Board Follow-ups](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/35681)
    
    "* [Economic Development & Diversity Compliance](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/32544)

    "* [Employment at BCPS](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/12469)

    "* [School Directory](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/13385)

    "* [Academics](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/31868)
    * [Applied Learning (Academic Electives, Specials & Magnet Programs)](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/13621)
    * [Diversity & School Climate ( formerly School Climate & Discipline)](https://www.browardschools.com/Domain/13726)

    "* [Contact](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/13426)

    "

    "* [Office of School Performance and Accountability (OSPA)](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/13616)

    "* [Announcements](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/12376)

    "* [Academics](https://www.browardschools.com/Page/31868)

    "* [Superintendent](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/14022)

    "* [\*Information and Resources](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/12430)

    "

    "* [Pages with Left Nav Disabled](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/13943)

    "

    "

    "* [Testing Channel](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/25356)

    "* [Choose BCPCS](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/26056)

    "* [2024/25 School Choice](https://www.browardschools.com/schoolchoice)

    "

    "* [JA World](https://www.browardschools.com/domain/25581)

Search 

Popular Topics
--------------

* 

School Resources
----------------

* 
* 

* 
* 
* Overview

Website Privacy Policy
======================

* The School Board of Broward County, Florida recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this website. Information may be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the State of Florida's archiving policies. It is the policy of the State of Florida that all state records are open for public inspection. This policy is embodied in the Florida Constitution, together with the right of an individual to be free from unauthorized governmental intrusion into their private life, as provided in Article I, Section 23. In recognition of these policies, The School Board of Broward County, Florida has established this Internet Privacy Policy. When you use The School Board of Broward County, Florida's website, you are acknowledging that the personal information you provide is subject to Florida's Public Records Policy as stated in Chapter 119, Florida Statutes, and Article I, Section 24 of the Florida Constitution.  
      
    **Consent to this Privacy Policy**  
    By using our website, you signify that you agree with the terms of our privacy policy as posted in this area of the site. If you do not agree with the privacy policy, do not provide any information personal or otherwise. If you choose not to provide personal information on this site, you may not be able to do certain things, like access particular parts of the site or send us e-mail.  
      
    **Collection of Personal Information**  
    As used in the privacy policy, “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information such as the name, street address, credit card number, screen name and e-mail address of yourself or customers. The site you entered may collect some of all of these types of personal information. Be assured The School Board of Broward County, Florida will not collect any personal information from your visits unless you provide the information voluntarily.
    
    When you provide us with personal information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy, which includes your right to limit our use of the personal information as described in this policy.  
      
    **How We Use Your Information**  
    When you supply Personal Information at this website, the product whose site you entered will use for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to provide you with a specific service or to send you a message). It may also be used by the products whose site you entered, as well as by our other vendors, to contact you regarding other products and services that may be of interest to you. At any time, you may opt out of such future contact. (See “Who to contact below.)
    
    At times we may retain third parties to analyze data we collect on our web sites, including Personal Information, solely to help us improve our products and our web sites. Third parties vendors are only authorized by us to use your Personal Information as outlined in their agreement and not in any other way.
    
    Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order.  
      
    **Use of Email Addresses**  
    Pursuant to Chapter 668, Florida Statutes, Public records status of e-mail addresses; agency website notice.—Any agency, as defined in s. 119.011, or legislative entity that operates a website and uses electronic mail shall post the following statement in a conspicuous location on its website: Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.
    
    Users do not have to provide personal information to visit The School Board of Broward County, Florida’s website, download publications, and use e-mail communications. Personal information will not be collected unless the user chooses to provide this information to The School Board of Broward County, Florida.
    
    Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity online. Instead, you will need to use a non-web option for transacting that business with The School Board of Broward County, Florida.
    
    Any information provided by you to The School Board of Broward County, Florida, including, but not limited to, feedback, questions, comments, and suggestions are non-confidential; moreover, such information is a public record subject to public inspection pursuant to law. The School Board of Broward County, Florida has no obligation of any kind with respect to such information and is free to reproduce, use, and disclose the information to others without limitation. Additionally, The School Board of Broward County, Florida is free to use any ideas, concepts, etc. contained in such information for any purpose whatsoever.
    
    **Children**  
    Regulations enacted in April 2000 under the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act give children under 13 years of age greater privacy protection online. Children's privacy is of primary concern to The School Board of Broward County, Florida, and this policy along with adopted School Board policies and practices reflect applicable laws and regulations on children's privacy. Save for student and educational records, The School Board of Broward County, Florida does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.
    
    **Use of "Cookies"**  
    When you visit The School Board of Broward County, Florida’s website, you can surf the site anonymously and access information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we may use "cookies" to assist your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. The data allows your browser to communicate with our web servers. However, it cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, if you do not accept cookies, you will not be able to use some of our functions that require their use.
    
    For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages. While certain Web pages use cookies to assist your visit to The School Board of Broward County, Florida’s website, and while our web servers automatically log the IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally, and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided personal information to a specific web page.  
      
    **Links to Other Sites**  
    Information, data or material accessible via The School Board of Broward County, Florida's World Wide Web pages may contain hyperlinks to information, data or material held on networked information services beyond The School Board of Broward County, Florida's web pages. The School Board of Broward County, Florida makes no warranty, or guarantee of promise, express or implied, that the data, or material accessible via the hyperlinks contained on The School Board of Broward County, Florida's web pages is accurate, complete, up to date, or fit for any use whatsoever, nor represents or implies that its use will not infringe privately held rights. As such, The School Board of Broward County, Florida is not responsible for the content of any off-site material referenced from hypertext documents via The School Board of Broward County, Florida’s web pages. Use of information from those websites is voluntary. References at those websites to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, or otherwise, does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, affiliation, or favoring by the Official Site of The School Board of Broward County, Florida. When you link to another site you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
    
    **NOTICE: FOR IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT SAFE SURFING FROM THE FEDERAL TRADE COMMISSION REFER TO: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.html.**
    
    As required by Section 668.6076, Florida Statutes, you are hereby notified that:
    
    Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.  
    Jurisdictional Issues
    
    This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida as it is applied to contracts entered into by residents of the State of Florida including the public records law, found in Chapter 119, Florida Statutes. You also consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state courts in Broward County, Florida, and you further consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction of the courts therein.
    
    If any provision(s) of this Privacy Policy are found to be contrary to law, then such provision(s) shall be construed, as nearly as possible, to reflect the intentions of the parties with the other provisions remaining in full force and effect.
    
    The School Board of Broward County, Florida's failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the policy shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision unless acknowledged and agreed to by The School Board of Broward County, Florida in writing.
    
    The section titles in this Privacy Policy are solely used for the convenience of the parties and have no legal or contractual significance. This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and The School Board of Broward County, Florida with respect to the subject matter herein and supersede any and all prior or contemporaneous oral or written agreements. You may not assign this agreement to any other party.
    
    **Who to Contact**  
    Please contact us at [todd.sussman@browardschools.com](mailto:todd.sussman@browardschools.com "Email Todd Sussman") or if you have any questions about this policy or to report any violations of the privacy policy. We will respond in a timely manner.

Contact Information
===================

* Equal Educational Opportunities/ADA Compliance
    
    600 SE Third Avenue
    
    Fort Lauderdale, Florida 33301
    
    Phone: [754-321-2150](tel:754-321-2150)
    
    Fax: 754-321-2714
    
    TTL: 754-321-2158
    
    Phone: [\--](tel:--)
    
    Wladimir G. Alvarez
    
    Director

Privacy and Legal Notices
=========================

Last Modified on August 8, 2018

Visit Us
--------

Kathleen C. Wright (KCW)  
Administration Center  
600 S.E. Third Avenue

Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301

[Get Directions](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Kathleen%20C.%20Wright%20(KCW)%20%3Cbr%20/%3EAdministration%20Center%3Cbr%20/%3E600%20S.E.%20Third%20Avenue+Fort%20Lauderdale,+FL+33301)

Contact Us
----------

Fax

Contact Us
----------

Fax

All Content © Broward County Public Schools

* 

Copyright © 2024 Finalsite - all rights reserved.
